[Music]
the ceremony is oh no lady dodo how did
you manage to do this you just couldn't
stay away could you soon be gone for 5
minutes and here you are injecting
yourself from
Poison
dodo what are you telling me what are
you saying what you didn't do this dodo
did somebody do this to you lady dodo
who did this to you tell me who did this
the wallpaper
the Wayne scotting No the Sati the Rodan
sculpture the Triceratops fossil the
gold Pelican vase the Zulu hunting spear
the chair the chair chair have you
counted the towels recently chair gave
her to me she's in the meat locker she
did what are you doing out here you
muskrat the com called out the name
Seline sir I'm the new servant girl
Seline I want the money I want the fame
I want the whole world to know my name
this is mine I got to get it I got to
get it got to get it